<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>Jason Evans</title>
  <link href="http://jasonevans1.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://jasonevans1.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2011-09-07T07:03:09-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://jasonevans1.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Jason Evans</name>
    
  </author>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Vagrant Magento Update</title>
    <link href="http://jasonevans1.github.com/blog/2011/09/07/vagrant-magento-update/"/>
    <updated>2011-09-07T06:58:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://jasonevans1.github.com/blog/2011/09/07/vagrant-magento-update</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have updated the (https://github.com/jasonevans1/vagrant-magento)[vagrant-magento project] to install Magento 1.6.0.0.   Enjoy and let me know of any changes you would like to see.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Active Projects</title>
    <link href="http://jasonevans1.github.com/blog/2011/09/05/active-projects/"/>
    <updated>2011-09-05T14:33:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://jasonevans1.github.com/blog/2011/09/05/active-projects</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Below are the github projects I have worked on in the past 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Projects&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jasonevans1/Aoe_Scheduler&quot;&gt;Aoe Scheduler&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a fork of the Magento extension that adds a scheduler interface to Magento's admin panel.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fabrizio-branca.de/magento-cron-scheduler.html&quot;&gt;More info on Aoe_Scheduler&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have forked this extension to support adding and updating tasks.  I have also added support for setting optional parameters with a task.  I have submitted a pull request to Fabrizio Branca.  He has asked from some changes that I will be implementing in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this extension will provide a needed feature in Magento.  If you have any suggestions or comments please send me a message in github.  Here is my github profile &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jasonevans1&quot;&gt;@jasonevans1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jasonevans1/vagrant-magento&quot;&gt;Vagrant Magento&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created this project to learn Vagrant and Puppet.  Since I do Magento development daily, I thought it would be useful to have a Vagrant box with Magento installed.
This project provides a foundation for developing with Magento Commerce in a Vagrant box. The machine is based on CentOS 5.5. It contains puppet modules for provisioning a server with Magento installed.&lt;br/&gt;
List of installed software.
* Magento Community Edition - 1.5.1.0
* Mysql
* Zend Server Community Edition - PHP 5.3
* xdebug
* phpunit
Note: I intend to update this project to install the latest version of Magento with 1.6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jasonevans1/iodocs&quot;&gt;iodocs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a fork of the iodocs project from Mashery.  I have added support for basic username and password auth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I forked this project to learn more about node.js.  I am very interested in learning more about node.js.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
